Vicente Rubén Borjas Machado

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthdate: November 23, 1989

Nationality: Venezuelan Phone: +56 9 7271 3587

E-mail: vrborjasm@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/vrborjasm

Address: Escuela Agrícola,

607F Macul, Chile

RESUME

I'm a developer and gamer, from Venezuela. Now GENERAL Living in Santiago de Chile, Chile. With experience front-end and a little in back-end. I am interested in learning new technologies, always trying to follow the best practices of each new language and framework. I enjoy front-end development, and work for good details and a good user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

PAYKU | September 2020 - Currently

Front-end development of a platform of payment system using React, redux and Bootstrap.

BENCHMARKING DEVELOPER

GEPRO | January 2020 - April 2020

Full-stack development of a platform of benchmarking using React, Redux as tools and Material UI, such as back-end development through Node, Express and sequelize.

MAINTENANCE ENGINEER

PONTIFICIA UNIVERSIDAD CATOLICA DE CHILE | 2018 - 2020

Preparation and coordination of maintenance plans for the equipment found in the teaching laboratories of the Faculty of development of small applications to improve the control and order of the laboratory equipment.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING TECH

Professional Institute AIEP | Santiago, Chile

March 2019 - Currently

ELECTRICAL ENGINEER

Universidad Central de Venezuela | Caracas, Venezuela July 2009 - April 2017

SKILLS

- Responsibility
- Efficient communication
- Ability to Work in a Team
- Puntuality
- Autodidact
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- HTML
- CSS
- ES6+/JavaScript

TOOLS

- Git
- npm
- Bootstrap
- Foundation
- React
- NextJS
- Redux
- Ruby on Rails
- Node JS
- Express
- Sequelize
- Firebase
- Material UI

LANGUAGES

- Native Spanish
- English Advance Level
- Portugues Medium Level